A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.29 (A2003) FA490
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2003.087: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2004; AC.2003.087; 9.17 Cubic Feet 7 standard record storage boxes, R3595-R3601.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.087.1; 9.17 Cubic Feet 7 record storage boxes
    - RF 97013 #19 - KAHN, KATHLEEN - FIELD SITE REPORT ON DEMOGRAPHICS AND HEALTH RESEARCH, 1997-1999 (Box R3600)
    - RF 97016 #170 - UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS (AUSTIN) - PARALLEL CANTOS EXHIBITION, 1997-1999 (Box R3600)
    - RF 97016 #177 - ROGERS MUSEUM - "BARELA: ARTISTA POPULAR DEL PUEBLO", 1994-2000 (Box R3600)
    - RF 94063 #16; RF 97018 #17 - STEEL VALLEY AUTHORITY - PENSION FUNDS AND COMMUNITY INVESTMENTS; INVESTMENT STRATEGY IN REGIONAL ECONOMIC MARKETS, 1997-1998 (Box R3601)
    - RF 97016 #184 - HISTORIC HUDSON VALLEY - REINTERPRETING PHILIPSBURG MANNER, 1995-1999 (Box R3601)
    - RF 97016 #186 - COLUMBIA COLLEGE (CHICAGO) - EXHIBITION OF KOREAN IMAGES AND INSTALLATIONS, 1997-2002 (Box R3601)
    - RF 97016 #188 - UNIVERSITY OF NEW ORLEANS - SYMPOSIUM, "BOUNDARIES, BARRIERS AND BRIDGES: CREATING INCLUSIVE AUDIENCES FOR SOUTHERN ART", 1997-2002 (Box R3601)
    - RF 97016 #189 - MUSEO DE LAS AMERICAS - EXHIBITION, "1598, 1848, 1898: CONFLICTS, CONQUEST AND CONSEQUENCES", 1997-2002 (Box R3601)
    - RF 97016 #190 - UNIVERSITY OF SOUTH CAROLINA - EXHIBITION, "I MADE THIS JAR", 1997-2002 (Box R3601)
    - RF 97016 #191 - STOREFRONT FOR ART AND ARCHITECTURE - DETROIT PROJECT, "HOME: MADE IN DETROIT", 1997-2002 (Box R3601)
    - RF 97017 #86 - CLEVELAND STATE UNIVERSITY - SCHOOL DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM REGIONAL TRAINING CENTER, 1997-2002 (Box R3601)
    - RF 97017 #90 - SAN FRANCISCO STATE UNIVERSITY - ESTABLISH A BAY AREA SCHOOL DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM REGIONAL TRAINING CENTER, 1994-2001 (Box R3601)
    - RF 97017 #93 - SAN DIEGO CITY SCHOOLS - COMER PROGRAM EFFECTIVENESS, 1996-2000 (Box R3601)
- AC.2003.099: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1992-2003; AC.2003.099; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 standard record storage boxes, R3602-R3606,
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.099.1; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - RF 97019 #11 - COMMUNICATIONS CONSORTIUM MEDIA CENTER - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1998-2000 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #31 - STEPHAN, WILLIAM B. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP, 1997-2001 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97021 #58 - BILGI UNIVERSITY (TURKEY) - EXHIBITION, "MODERNITIES AND MEMORIES: RECENT WORKS FROM ISLAMIC WORLD", 1998-2000 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #268 - CHO, SEOUNGHO - VIDEO, "DESERT PROJECT", 1998-2002 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #269 - VELEZ, EDIN - DOCUMENTARY, "OF EVERY HUE AND CAST: ANOTHER HISTORY OF AMERICAN ART", 1998-2002 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #270 - DEFELICIANTONIO, TINA - DOCUMENTARY, "SILENT VOICES", 1998-1999 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #271 - DUNYE, CHERYL - FILM, "THE PRISON PROJECT", 1998-2002 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #272 - HAMILTON, AVA - DOCUMENTARY, "CHEYENNE DOG SOLDIERS STORY", 1998-1999 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #273 - KALIN, TOM - "SOME DESPERATE CRIME ON MY HEAD OR ALFRED CHESTER'S WIG", 1998-2002 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #275 - KIM-GIBSON, DAI SIL - DOCUMENTARY, "JAPANESE MILITARY SUPPLIES: KOREAN COMFORT WOMEN", 1998-2002 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #277 - KUCHAR, GEORGE - "THE SHADOW PEOPLE, BASED ON THE LIFE OF JOHN KEEL, 1998-2000 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #278 - LEWIS, ANNE - "MORRISTOWN" A DOCUMENTARY, 1998-1999 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #279 - MENKES, NINA - NARRATIVE FILM, "HEATSTROKE", 1998-2002 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #280 - RIVERA, ALEX - "WHY CYBRACEROS", 1998-2003 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #281 - SONNERBORN, BARBARA - DOCUMENTARY ON VIETNAM, "REGRET TO INFORM", 1998-2002 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #282 - RUIZ, MARIA SANTIAGO - VIDEO SERIES, BASHU'AN GUIOU (THE OWNER OF THE MOUNTAIN), 1998-2002 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #283 - SUTER, GERARDO - VIDEO INSTALLATION, "TRANSITUS", 1998-2002 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #284 - URRUSTI, JUAN FRANCISCO - DOCUMENTARY, "LA GRIETA" (THE FISSURE)", 1998-2000 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #287 - INTERNATIONAL MEDIA RESOURCE EXCHANGE - EXPAND ONLINE DATABASE AND DISTRIBUTION SERVICES, 1996-1999 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #288 - FOUNDATION FOR INDEPENDENT FILM AND VIDEO - WEB SITE DEVELOPMENT, 1997-2002 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #290 - MCGILL UNIVERSITY (CANADA) - STUDY INNOVATION IN DIGITAL CULTURE, 1998-2000 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97022 #291 - MEISELAS, SUSAN - WEBSITE FOR CULTURAL EXCHANGE, WWW.AKAKURDISTAN.COM, 1998-2002 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97023 #340 - AMERICAN CONSERVATORY THEATRE FOUNDATION - "BETHLEHEM", A PLAY, 1998-2002 (Box R3602)
    - RF 97024 #59 - OPEN WINDOW NETWORK (SOUTH AFRICA) - PARTICIPATION OF AFRICAN DELEGATES AT 1998 VIDEAZIMUT EVENTS, 1998-2000 (Box R3602)
    - RF 96040 #58; RF 97024 #60 - WOMEN'S WORLD ORGANIZATION FOR RIGHTS, LITERATURE AND DEVELOPMENT - WOMEN'S LITERATURE AND CIVIL SOCIETY IN EAST AFRICA, 1997-1999 (Box R3603)
    - RF 97024 #61 - ASSOCIATION DE LA PLUME NOIR (FRANCE) - FOURTH LITERARY SALON, 1998-1999 (Box R3603)
    - RF 97024 #63 - FILM AND TV MARKET INITIATIVE (SOUTH AFRICA) - TRAINING WORKSHOPS; PARTICIPATION OF AFRICANS AT "SITHENGI 98", 1998-1999 (Box R3603)
    - RF 97024 #64 - CONTEMPORARY AFRICAN MUSIC ARTS TRUST (SOUTH AFRICA) - "JAZZ AFRICA", 1998-2001 (Box R3603)
    - RF 97024 #65 - CASA VIA MAGIA (BRAZIL) - "SECOND CELEBRATION OF AFRICAN HERITAGE", 1998-1999 (Box R3603)
    - RF 97024 #68 - PANOS INSTITUTE - PILOT PROGRAM: STRENGTHEN INDEPENDENT RADIO IN WEST AFRICA, 1992-2000 (Box R3604, Box R3603)
    - RF 97024 #68 - PANOS INSTITUTE - PILOT PROGRAM: STRENGTHEN INDEPENDENT RADIO IN WEST AFRICA - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1992-2000 (Box R3604, Box R3603)
    - RF 97025 #42 - ALBUQUERQUE PUBLIC SCHOOLS - BUILDING AN INFRASTRUCTURE FOR PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT, 1994-2000; 2003 (Box R3604, Box R3605)
    - RF 97026 #16 - AMERICAN LAND INSTITUTE - SOCIOECONOMIC MAPPING OF LOS ANGELES METROPOLITAN AREA, 1996-2003 (Box R3605)
    - RF 97027 #1 - CONSENSUS ORGANIZING INSTITUTE - REGIONAL ECONOMIC AND COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT, 1997-1998; 2003 (Box R3605)
    - RF 97027 #6 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR ECONOMIC ALTERNATIVES - NATIONAL SURVEY, 1996-2001 (Box R3605)
    - RF 97031 #515 - BEIJING HUI LONG GUAN HOSPITAL (CHINA) - HEALTH SOCIAL SCIENCE COURSE, 1997-1999 (Box R3605)
    - RF 97031 #517 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY-- 1998 WORKSHOP ON BURDEN OF DISEASE, 1997-1999 (Box R3605)
    - RF 97031 #518 - INCLEN, INC. - SECOND EVALUATION, 1998-2003 (Box R3605)
    - RF 97031 #519 - SREE CHITRA TIRUNAL INSTITUTE FOR MEDICAL SCIENCES AND TECHNOLOGY (INDIA) - ATTEND INCLEN XVI GLOBAL MEETING IN BANGKOK, 1998-2003 (Box R3605)
    - RF 97032 #121 - CENTER FOR STUDY OF RESPONSIVE LAW - AIDS-RELATED AND OTHER ESSENTIAL MEDICINES, 1999-2001 (Box R3605)
    - RF 97032 #121 - CENTER FOR STUDY OF RESPONSIVE LAW - AIDS-RELATED AND OTHER ESSENTIAL MEDICINES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1999-2001 (Box R3605)
    - RF 97032 #122 - KENYA MEDICAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - OUTPATIENT CLINICAL MANAGEMENT OF HIV, 1996-1999 (Box R3605)
    - RF 97033 #62 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - FIELD SUPERVISOR' WORKSHOP, 1997-1999 (Box R3605)
    - RF 97033 #63 - CHULALONGKORN UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - EDUCATIONAL MODULES BASED ON PUBLIC HEALTH, 1998-2003 (Box R3605)
    - RF 97033 #65 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - QUALITY ASSURANCE MANAGEMENT METHODS COURSE, 1995-2001 (Box R3605)
    - RF 98013 #156 - (POLICY RESEARCH AND DIALOGUE) - EVALUATION OF NGO'S INFORMATIONAL AND EDUCATIONAL ACTIVITIES, 1998-2001 (Box R3606)
    - RF 98013 #156 - (POLICY RESEARCH AND DIALOGUE) - EVALUATION OF NGO'S INFORMATIONAL AND EDUCATIONAL ACTIVITIES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1998-2001 (Box R3606)
- AC.2003.100: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1983-2003; AC.2003.100; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes, R3607-R3612.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.100.1; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 record storage boxes
    - RF 97033 #66 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - NETWORK ACTIVITIES AMONG PHSWOW SITES, 1997-2000 (Box R3607)
    - RF 97038 - CORPORATION FOR SUPPORTIVE HOUSING - INCREASE EMPLOYMENT OPPORTUNITIES FOR SUPPORTIVE HOUSING RESIDENTS, 1993-1998 (Box R3608, Box R3607)
    - RF 97038 - CORPORATION FOR SUPPORTIVE HOUSING - INCREASE EMPLOYMENT OPPORTUNITIES FOR SUPPORTIVE HOUSING RESIDENTS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1993-1998 (Box R3608, Box R3607)
    - RF 97041 - 651, AN ARTS CENTER - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1997-1999 (Box R3609)
    - RF 97042 #5 - CARTER CENTER - FOOD SECURITY FOR NORTH KOREA, 1998-2000 (Box R3609)
    - RF 97044 #22 - UNITED NATIONS - WHO - VACCINE DEVELOPMENT, 1983-1999 (Box R3610, Box R3609)
    - RF 97044 #22 - UNITED NATIONS - WHO - VACCINE DEVELOPMENT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1983-1999 (Box R3610, Box R3609)
    - RF 97044 #28 - PAN AMERICAN HEALTH ORGANIZATION - MEETING ON VACCINES IN CHILE, 1999-2001 (Box R3611)
    - RF 97044 #29 - (VACCINES) - MEETINGS ON VACCINES IN INDIA AND BELLAGIO, 1999-2000 (Box R3611)
    - RF 97047 #129 - ZAMBIA ASSOCIATION FOR WOMEN IN SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY - PUBLICATION ON WOMEN WITH CAREERS IN SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY, 1998-2000 (Box R3611)
    - RF 97047 #134 - THIRD WORLD ORGANIZATION FOR WOMEN IN SCIENCE (ITALY) - GENERAL ASSEMBLY AND CONFERENCE ON WOMEN FOR SUSTAINABLE HUMAN DEVELOPMENT IN CAPE TOWN, 1998-2000 (Box R3611)
    - RF 97047 #138 - GENDER AND SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY ASSOCIATION (GASAT) (INDIA) - NINTH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE, 1998-2000 (Box R3611)
    - RF 97047 #142 - CITY COUNCIL OF KAMPALA (UGANDA) - MINDS ACROSS AFRICA SCHOOL CLUBS PROJECT, 1999 (Box R3611)
    - RF 97047 #144 - HYDE, KARIN - TO PRESENT A PAPER ON ROLE OF COMMUNITY SCHOOLS AND EDUCATION IN AFRICA AT OXFORD CONFERENCE (RESCINDED), 1999 (Box R3611)
    - RF 97048 - ATLANTIC COUNCIL - KOREAN ROADMAP FOR NORMALIZATION, 1996-1999 (Box R3611)
    - RF 97050 #4 - CHILDREN'S DEFENSE FUND - SERIES OF DIALOGUES ON CHILDREN, RACE AND POVERTY, 1998-2001 (Box R3611)
    - RF 97050 #10 - MEXICAN AMERICAN LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATIONAL FUND - INFORM CALIFORNIA MULTI-ETHNIC COMMUNITIES OF CONSEQUENCES OF PROPOSITION, 1997-2002 (Box R3612)
    - RF 97050 #11 - FRED FRIENDLY SEMINARS - TELEVISION SEMINAR, "RACE, EQUALITY, OPPORTUNITY: AFFIRMATIVE ACTION IN AMERICA", 1998-2000 (Box R3612)
    - RF 97050 #11 - FRED FRIENDLY SEMINARS - TELEVISION SEMINAR, "RACE, EQUALITY, OPPORTUNITY: AFFIRMATIVE ACTION IN AMERICA" - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1998-2000 (Box R3612)
    - RF 97050 #16 - AMERICAN JEWISH COMMITTEE - COMMONQUEST MAGAZINE, 1997-1999 (Box R3612)
    - RF 97050 #8 - STUBBLEFIELD FOUNDATION - REALITY WORKS: AMERICAN DREAM DEFERRED DOCUMENTARY, 1998-2000 (Box R3612)
    - RF 97052 #597 - UNIVERSITY OF PUERTO RICO (COLLEGE OF HUMANITIES) - HUMANITIES RESIDENCY FELLOWSHIPS - CARIBBEAN 2000, 1994-2000 (Box R3612)
    - RF 97052 #598 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - PUBLIC PROGRAMMING AND COMMUNITY OUTREACH FOR ASIAN/PACIFIC/AMERICAN STUDIES PROGRAM AND INSTITUTE, 1998-2001 (Box R3612)
    - RF 97055 #116 - LINCOLN CENTER FOR THE PERFORMING ARTS - "LINCOLN CENTER FESTIVAL 98", 1997-2002 (Box R3612)
    - RF 97055 #117 - CULTURAL COUNCIL OF JACKSON HOLE - HISPANIC CULTURAL FESTIVAL, 1997-2000 (Box R3612)
- AC.2003.107: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2003; AC.2003.107; 10.48 Cubic Feet 8 standard record storage boxes, R3613-R3615 and R3619-R3623.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.107.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - RF 97055 #120 - POINT COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT CORP. - "ALL THAT DRAMA" THEATER CONFERENCE AND FESTIVAL, 1998-1999 (Box R3613)
    - RF 97055 #127 - CHICAGO CARIBBEAN ARTS ASSOCIATION - "PUERTO RICAN CUATRO CONFERENCE AND FESTIVAL", 1998-2002 (Box R3613)
    - RF 97055 #129 - NEW JERSEY PERFORMING ARTS CENTER CORP. - "INVENTING AMERICA: MEMORY, WORK, SPIRIT", 1998-1999 (Box R3613)
    - RF 97055 #130 - IDRIS ACKAMOOR AND CULTURAL ODYSSEY - ACTIVITIES OF 1999 "AFRICAN-AMERICAN PERFORMANCE ART FESTIVAL", 1998-1999 (Box R3613)
    - RF 97058 #3 - URBAN INSTITUTE - COMMUNITY-BUILDING POLICY CENTER, 1997-2001 (Box R3613)
    - RF 98001 #610 - SCRIPPS RESEARCH INSTITUTE - MOLECULAR BIOLOGY OF RICE VIRUSES, 1991-2002 (Box R3613)
    - RF 98001 #610 - SCRIPPS RESEARCH INSTITUTE - MOLECULAR BIOLOGY OF RICE VIRUSES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1991-2002 (Box R3613)
    - RF 98001 #611 - TEXAS TECH UNIVERSITY - ROOT PENETRATION IN RICE ANALYSIS, 1990-2001 (Box R3613)
    - RF 98001 #623 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR P. GOMATHINAYAGAM, 1994-1998 (Box R3613)
    - RF 98001 #629 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - RICE BLAST POPULATIONS AND RESISTANCE GENES, 1997-2002 (Box R3613)
    - RF 98001 #630 - CLEMSON UNIVERSITY - BACTERIAL ARTIFICIAL CHROMOSOME (BAG) LIBRARY FOR MAPPING RICE GENOME, 1997-1999 (Box R3613)
    - RF 98001 #648 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - WORKSHOP ON RICE IN WATER-LIMITED ENVIRONMENTS, 1998-1999 (Box R3614)
    - RF 98001 #659 - PUNJAB AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - TISSUE CULTURE AND GENETIC TRANSFORMATION OF BASMATI AND INDICA RICE, 1997-1998 (Box R3614)
    - RF 98001 #662 - PHILIPPINE RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR THERESA PERALTA, 1998-1999 (Box R3614)
    - RF 98001 #675 - SPIC SCIENCE FOUNDATION (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR GEORGE THOMAS, 1995-1999 (Box R3614)
    - RF 98001 #684 - COMMONWEALTH SCIENTIFIC AND INDUSTRIAL RESEARCH ORGANIZATION - RAGGED STUNT VIRUS, 1988-1999 (Box R3614)
    - RF 98001 #692 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - RICE TRANSFORMATION RESEARCH AND TRAINING FOR S.R. SIKDAR, 1998-1999 (Box R3614)
    - RF 98001 #701 - TATA INSTITUTE FOR FUNDAMENTAL RESEARCH (INDIA) - NATIONAL RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY NETWORK EIGHTH MEETING, 1997-1999 (Box R3614)
    - RF 98005 #158 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - CHANGING STRUCTURE OF MALAWI'S FOOD SYSTEM, 1998-2000 (Box R3614)
    - RF 98005 #161 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - SIXTH EASTERN AND SOUTHERN AFRICA REGIONAL MAIZE CONFERENCE, 1998-1999 (Box R3614)
    - RF 98005 #169 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - RHIZOBIUM ECOLOGY NETWORK OF EAST AND SOUTHERN AFRICA (RENEASA), 1997-2002 (Box R3614)
    - RF 98005 #170 - VILLAGE ENTERPRISE ZONE ASSOCIATIONS INTERNATIONAL INC. - ASSISl CHITEDZE AGRICULTURAL RESOURCE STATION IN MALAWI WITH MAIZE FERTILIZER TRIALS, 1994-2000 (Box R3614)
    - RF 98005 #173 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - ECONOMIC POTENTIAL OF SMALLHOLDER SOYABEAN PRODUCTION, 1998-2001 (Box R3614)
    - RF 98005 #176 - MALAWI - AGRICULTURE AND IRRIGATION (MINISTRY OF) - MALAWI GRAIN LEGUMES STUDY, 1998-2001 (Box R3614)
    - RF 98006 #30 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - RESEARCH PRODUCTIVITY AND RETURNS TO RESEARCH INVESTMENT ON STRIGA IN WESTERN KENYA, 1998 (Box R3614)
    - RF 98006 #34 - UNIVERSITY OF CHICAGO - PRODUCTION CONTROL OF MAIZE STRIGA SEED GERMINATION STIMULANT, 1996-1999 (Box R3614)
    - RF 98009 #9 - NWEKE, FELIX I. - CAREER DEVELOPMENT FELLOWSHIP IN AGRICULTURE, 1994-2001 (Box R3615)
    - RF 98012 #18 - UNIVERSITY OF DELHI (INDIA} - CONVENE PANEL OF EXPERTS TO PREPARE REPORT FOR EVALUATION OF INDIAN AND IMPORTED TRANSGENIC PLANT MATERIAL, 1998-1999 (Box R3615)
    - RF 98006 #40 - INTERNATIONAL CROPS RESEARCH INSTITUTE FOR THE SEMI-ARID TROPICS (INDIA) - WORKSHOP/SEMINAR - MOLECULAR MARKERS AND STRIGA-RESISTANT CEREAL, 1999-2000 (Box R3615)
    - RF 98007 #42 - KENYA AG RICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - BANANA PLANTLET DISTRIBUTION TO SMALLHOLDERS, 1996-2001 (Box R3615)
    - RF 98008 #115 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - SOIL EROSION AND LANDSLIDES, 1998-2001 (Box R3615)
    - RF 98008 #119 - EGERTON UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - ABNORMAL RAINS AND FARMING STRATEGIES AND EL-NINO PHENOMENA, 1998-2002 (Box R3615)
    - RF 98008 #120 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - EVALUATION OF IRRIGATION POWER/ENERGY SYSTEMS, 1998-2001 (Box R3615)
    - RF 98008 #126 - (FORUM ON AGRICULTURAL RESOURCE HUSBANDRY) - THIRD BIENNIAL JOINT MEETING OF THE FORUM, 1998-1999 (Box R3615)
    - RF 98008 #129 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - EROSION IN BANANA-BASED MICRO-CATCHMENT OF LAKE VICTORIA BASIN, 1997-2001 (Box R3615)
    - RF 98011 #35 - KASETSART UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR YEETOH DABBHADATTA, 1998-2002 (Box R3615)
    - RF 98011 #37 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - STRIGA RESISTANCE IN SORGHUM RESEARCH, 1998-1999 (Box R3615)
    - RF 98013 #177 - DEUTSCHE STIFTUNG WELTBEVOLKERUNG (GERMANY) - COMMUNICATION ON POPULATION POLICY ISSUES, 1994-2000 (Box R3615)
    - RF 98013 #183 - POPULATION REFERENCE BUREAU - CASE STUDIES CONCERNING IMPLEMENTATION OF 1994 ICPD RECOMMENDATIONS, 1997-1999 (Box R3615)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 record storage boxes
    - SCHOLARS (ADAMS, JULIAN PHILIP) (CO-RESIDENT: CASTILLA, EDUARDO ENRIQUE), 1996-1998 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (ALONI, SHULAMIT), 1996-1998 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (AMIRKHANIAN, CHARLES), 1996-1997 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (AUSTIN, GRANVILLE S.), 1996-2000 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (BARUZZI, ROBERTO GERALDO), 1996-1997 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (BICKERTON, DEREK) (CO-RESIDENT: CALVIN, WILLIAM H.), 1996-2000 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (BIRD, KAI), 1996-2001 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (BONFIL, ROBERT), 1997-1998 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (BOTTRELL, DALE G.), 1996-1997 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (BRAMSON, PHYLLIS M.), 1997-1998 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (BRUZELIUS, CAROLINE), 1996-1997 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (CAPLAN, JANE), 1996-1998 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (CARRASQUILLA, GABRIEL), 1996-1999 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (CARTARESCU, MIRCEA), 1995-1997 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (CASTILLO MARTINEZ, JUVENAL J.), 1996-1997 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (CHAUDHURY, SUSHIL), 1996-1998 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (CHINN, MENZIE DAVID), 1996-1997 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (CLOVER, CAROL J.), 1996-1998 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (CONGDON, CONSTANCE), 1996-1997 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (CUETO, MARCOS), 1996-1997 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (CURRIER, NATHAN), 1997-1998 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (D'AGOSTINO, PETER), 1996-1999 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (DE SOUZA, LUCIA RIBEIRO), 1996-2002 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (DUNTON-DOWNER, LESLIE) (CO-RESIDENT: THOMAS, AUGUSTA READ), 1996-1999 (Box R3619)
    - SCHOLARS (EAGLESON, PETER S.), 1995-2003 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (ELAIGWU, J. ISAWA), 1997-1998 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (EPSTEIN, STEVEN A.), 1995-1997 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (EVANS, LLOYD THOMAS), 1996-1999 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (FERESU, SARA BAISAI), 1997-1999 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (FLORENZANO, RAMON URZUA), 1996-1999 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (FOLKENFLIK, ROBERT), 1996-1997 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (FRASCONI, ANTONIO), 1996-2000 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (FREEDMAN, SARAH WARSHAUER) (CO-RESIDENT: SIMONS, ELIZABETH RADIN), 1996-1999 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (FREGOSO, ROSA LINDA), 1996-1998 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (FRESE, LYNDA ANN), 1996-2000 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (FRIEDMANN, YOHANNAN), 1996-1997 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (GHOSH, PARTHA S.), 1996-1997 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (GINAT, JOSEPH), 1996-1998 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (GLASER, DONALD A.), 1996-1997 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (GOMEZ DE SOUZA, LUIZ ALBERTO), 1996-2003 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (GONZALEZ-CRUSSI, FRANK), 1996-1998 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (GRAHAM, DOUGLAS ARTHUR MONTROSE), 1996-1998 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (GRAHAM, GEORGE) (DID NOT GO), 1995-1997 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (GRAY, HERMAN S.), 1996-1998 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (GRAY, VIRGINIA H.) (CO-RESIDENT: LOWERY, DAVID), 1996-1997 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (GREENBERG, DOLORES), 1996-2000 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (GRILLI, ENZO R.), 1995-1998 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (HADDAD, MOHAMED) (CO-RESIDENT: KHELIFA, MOUNIR), 1997-1998 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (HAMMOND, NORMAN), 1995-1998 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (HEPBURN, ANTHONY CRAWFORD), 1996-1997 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (HICKS, DAVID), 1996-1997 (Box R3620)
    - SCHOLARS (HOWE, FLORENCE), 1997 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (HUNG, EVA), 1996-2001 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (IKE, CHUKWEMEKA), 1996-2001 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (JOKIK, WOLFGANG KARL), 1995-1997 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (JOU ANTHONY S.R.), 1996-1997 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (KABEER, NAILA), 1996-1997 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (KALIBOVA, KVETA), 1996-1997 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (KATZ, ELIHU), 1995-1998 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (KATZ, RUTH), 1995-1997 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (KEATING, MICHAEL JAMES), 1996-1997 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (KERNS, DAVID L.), 1997-1999 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (KHAZANOV, ANATOLY M.), 1995-1997 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (KOCH, KENNETH), 1996-1998 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (LATYNSKI, MAREK), 1996-1998 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (LAURENCE, JANET), 1995-1997 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (LAWSON, THOMAS), 1997-1998 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (LAZARUS-YEFEH, HAVA), 1996-1997 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (LAZZARO, CLAUDIA), 1996-1997 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (LEVINE, GEORGE), 1996-2002 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (LEVITIN, ALEXIS), 1995-1998 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (LEWIN, DAVID BENJAMIN), 1996-1998 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (LI XIANG-HUI) (CO-RESIDENT: PO TIEN), 1996-1997 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (McCUSKER, JOHN J.), 1996-2001 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (McMANUS, JAMES), 1997 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (MARCUS, JANE CONNOR), 1996-1997 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (MASON, KAREN OPPENHEIM), 1996-1997 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (MAYARAM, SHAIL), 1996-1997 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (MIN, YONG SOON), 1996-1998 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (MORGAN, PATRICK M.), 1996-2003 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (MORMINO, GARY R.), 1996-1997 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (MUIR, EDWARD W.), 1996-1997 (Box R3621)
    - SCHOLARS (NARANG, GOPI CHAND), 1996-1997 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (NARDI, PETER M.), 1996-1999 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (NOVAK, LORIE), 1996-2000 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (OLKIN, INGRAM), 1996-1997 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (OTTO, WALDEMAR), 1996-1997 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (PANIKER K. AYYAPPA), 1995-1997 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (PERSICO, JOSEPH E.), 1996-2002 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (PINHEIRO, MARILIA PULQUERIO FUTRE), 1996-1998 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (PORTER, ROSALIE PEDALINO), 1996-1998 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (PRELEC, KRSTO), 1996-1998 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (PRICE, MONROE E.), 1996-1997 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (QUATERMAIN, PETER ALAN), 1996-1998 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (RAFAEL, VINCENT LEUTERIO), 1996-1998 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (RAPHAEL, MARC LEE), 1994-1996 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (RAY, BHARATI), 1996-2002 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (ROCKBURNE, DOROTHEA G.), 1996-1998 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (ROGIN, MICHAEL PAUL), 1993-1996 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (RORTY, RICHARD), 1996-1997 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (SARASON, SEYMOUR B.), 1995-1999 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (SCHWARTZ, REGINA), 1996-1997 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (SCHWENDINGER, LAURA ELISE), 1996-1998 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (SCOTT, JAMES C.), 1996-1997 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (SCOTT, PETER DALE), 1997-2001 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (SERBIN, SERGEI IVANOVICH), 1996-1997 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (SHULMAN, ALIX KATES), 1996-1999 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (SICHERMAN, BARBARA), 1996-1997 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (SILVER, BRENDA R.), 1997-2000 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (SLATER, CANDACE), 1996-1997 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (SMITH, ANN DEAVERE), 1996-1997 (Box R3622)
    - SCHOLARS (SONTAG, SUSAN), 1996-1997 (Box R3623)
    - SCHOLARS (SPIEGEL, DAVID), 1995-2000 (Box R3623)
    - SCHOLARS (STIER, HAYA) (CO-RESIDENT: TIENDA, MARTA), 1995-1997 (Box R3623)
    - SCHOLARS (TAROZZI, BIANCA), 1996-1997 (Box R3623)
    - SCHOLARS (TICHI, CECELIA), 1997-1998 (Box R3623)
    - SCHOLARS (TOMORI, OYEWALE), 1996-1997 (Box R3623)
    - SCHOLARS (UKADIKE, N. FRANK), 1996-1997 (Box R3623)